<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-12-15T13:33:50-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Job Management &amp;amp; Tracking System (JMTS)</title><entry><title type="html">Introduction</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/job%20management/2019/12/02/introduction.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introduction" /><published>2019-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/job%20management/2019/12/02/introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/job%20management/2019/12/02/introduction.html">&lt;h2&gt;User Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
    The Job Management and Tracking System (JMTS) is a web based application 
    intended to be used as the central system that facilitates the processes 
    of recording, editing, viewing, reporting and tracking requisite data for 
    any job undertaken by an enterprise. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

    The system is intended to be used by authorised users only. An authorised 
    user shall be given predefined privileges. The intent behind the user privileges 
    component of the JMTS is to ensure that authorised users can only execute 
    predefined types of queries or tasks that are in accordance with the guidance 
    of relevant standard operational or quality system procedures. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

    Currently, the JMTS works best when it is accessed via a Google Chrome Browser 
    (or browsers, such as Chromium and Rockmelt, with a Google Chrome backend coding). 
    Other cutting edge browsers such as Mozilla Firefox and Safari will also 
    work reasonably well with the JMTS. Internet Explorer is not a recommended 
    browser to use when accessing the JMTS. This browser may negatively impact 
    on the intended user experience with the JMTS in ways such as faulty 
    Graphical User Interface (GUI) display, slow functionality and so on.   
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Desmond Bennett</name></author><category term="Job Management" /><summary type="html">User Guide The Job Management and Tracking System (JMTS) is a web based application intended to be used as the central system that facilitates the processes of recording, editing, viewing, reporting and tracking requisite data for any job undertaken by an enterprise.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Configuration</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/job%20management/2019/12/01/configuration.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Configuration" /><published>2019-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-12-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/job%20management/2019/12/01/configuration</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/job%20management/2019/12/01/configuration.html">&lt;p&gt;Configuration content coming soon…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Desmond Bennett</name></author><category term="Job Management" /><summary type="html">Configuration content coming soon…</summary></entry></feed>